Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[pensive music]
[horse whinnying]
[wind whistling]
[music continues]
- [man] Robert!
[shots firing]
- Thomas!
[firing continues]
Thomas!
It's just Rockefeller.
You doomed us all.
[music continues]
[gun cocks]
[shot firing]
[flames whooshing]
- Robert!
[pensive music]
Robert!
[fist knocking]
- [Officer] Hello!
Who's in there?
[Thomas grimaces]
Open this door!
The police, I am.
Open the door now.
[dramatic music]
[music continues]
[horse nickers]
- Whoa.
Whoa.
[water rippling]
- Howdy.
[chuckles] Whoa.
Kinda jumpy ain't
ya there, Mister?
[water rippling]
- Been awhile since
I seen anyone.
- Oh.
[grunting]
[urine splashing]
[pensive music]
[sighs]
- You know, I heard that Robert
E. Lee is going to rise up
and crush the north.
Make things right again.
♪ Gosh ♪
♪ God saved the south ♪
♪ Yankee bull shut your mouth ♪
Shut your mouth, Yankee!
[horse snorts]
Northern Cavalry horse,
magnificent creature.
I've not seen one since
the Northern aggression.
You ain't been to New
York lately, have ya?
[music continues]
You see, there's a
fellow from New York
that went and killed
himself a Rockefeller.
It's the largest
reward in history,
and we plan on collecting it.
[chuckles] So,
take your hands off
of that nag and rise them up,
real slow.
[water rippling]
[shots firing]
[horse whinnying]
[bullets whizzing]
[Thomas grunting]
[firing continues]
[guns clicking]
[pensive music]
[shot firing]
[music continues]
[somber music]
[flies buzzing]
[Thomas grunting]
[water rippling]
[Thomas grunts]
[buzzing continues]
[singer vocalizing]
[soft music]
[eagle calls]
[snake rattling]
[music continues]
[vocalizing continues]
[music fades]
[wind whistling]
[Thomas spits]
[townspeople chattering]
[pensive music]
[door creaks]
[man munching]
- We've been expectin' you.
[Thomas sighs]
- Sit.
[alcohol splashing]
Our map.
[wind whistling]
[man sighs]
- We want to hear
in your own words,
why we should let you join us.
- Uh...
[upbeat music]
[coins clinking]
[music continues]
- In the name of the Father,
the Son, the Holy Ghost,
your sins are cleansed.
Amen.
- Amen.
[upbeat music]
[singer vocalizing]
[water splashing]
[music softens]
[bell tolling]
[music continues]
- Loyalty is sacred.
Courage is revered,
and heed this warning.
Betrayal stains the soul.
[shutter clicks]
And its consequence,
a swift demise.
Choose wisely for our
bond is forged in honor,
and sealed in blood.
[wind whistling]
[shutter clicks]
Holy Mother,
the angels and all the
saints come to meet you.
Prepare yourself to be judged
as you go forth from
this life to the next.
[music continues]
[shutter clicks]
[panel thuds]
[rope creaking]
[music continues]
[shutter clicks]
[air whooshing]
- On three, two...
Oh, he looks just like
a little angel at peace,
on his way to heaven.
On three.
And two, one.
Action.
[gentle music]
[horse whinnying]
[music continues]
[music fades]
[horse whinnying]
[pensive music]
[paper crinkling]
[wagon rattling]
[dog barking]
[hooves clomping]
[townspeople chattering]
[upbeat saloon music]
[match strikes]
- Hoodoo, remember what I said
about having a poker face?
- [laughs] Well, I guess not.
- [Hoodoo] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Your play.
- I'll raise [chuckles].
- Call.
[music continues]
[patrons chattering]
[pensive music]
[upbeat saloon music continues]
- Excuse me?
The stable boy said I
should ask for Jericho.
- Jericho will be back soon.
- I'm looking for a man.
- This is interesting,
this book.
This is Bible.
You should try it.
Read it, it's good.
- I'm looking for Thomas Keller.
- He's not here.
He's six feet under his
mark in the graveyard.
Hung for murder months ago.
- Are you sure?
- I'm not lyin'.
The graveyard's on
the edge of town.
See for yourself.
[both laughing]
- Hi, can I help you?
- Yes.
We need a room for the night.
- And food.
- Yeah.
- Well, we have plenty
of food, but the room?
Afraid we're sold out.
- Is there anywhere
else in town?
- Sorry Ma'am, no.
This it.
- We've been ridin'
all day in the cold.
Please.
- Look, I'm not
supposed to do this,
but you can have
my room, no charge.
- No, I have money.
- Don't, don't,
don't [chuckles].
- Okay.
- Here.
[coins clinking]
- Oh, okay [chuckles].
- Bella?
- Yes?
- Everything all right?
- Yes, Sir.
Just helpin' the lady
out with the room.
- Thank you.
- Upstairs and on the right.
- [Grace] I'm hungry, Mama.
- Here you go.
Tide you over.
- Thank you.
- You are
more than welcome.
- [Valerie] Thank you.
[Ben coughs]
Come on, Grace.
We have a nice bed
to sleep in tonight.
[pensive music]
- [Mary] I'm all in.
- Oh, that too rich
for me [chuckles].
[upbeat saloon music]
- Where do you
reckon they're goin'?
- I don't know.
Polly just got back this
afternoon with that stranger.
I have no clue who he is.
- It's your lucky day.
I'm callin' it quits.
[poker chips clinking]
- All right, why is
everybody so tense?
- Some lady with a child
was askin' 'bout Thomas.
- You didn't say that earlier.
- I was busy readin'
the Bible, Bella.
- I need to tell my dad.
- But tell your daddy I
was readin' the Bible.
- They'll light a
candle for you, Ben.
Hope, watch the bar.
- All right .
- Well, looks like we're
in for a long night.
[door creaks]
- All right, sit
here, eat this bread.
Just don't turn around, okay?
[Valerie exhales]
[pensive music]
[Valerie gasping]
[music continues]
[alcohol sloshing]
[gasping continues]
[music continues]
- Mm.
Mm.
[music continues]
[gasping continues]
Mm.
Mom?
- Yes, baby?
- [Grace] I'm thirsty .
- Just hold on a minute, okay?
[pensive music]
[gasping continues]
[music continues]
[anticipatory music]
[gasping continues]
[pensive music]
[skin sizzling]
[gasping continues]
[crows cawing]
[shovels scraping]
- I already told, you
he's not in there.
- I have to be sure.
Move faster.
Come on.
[shovel clinks]
- [Digger] I hit it .
- Open it.
[dirt clattering]
[wind whistling]
[music continues]
Told you.
[gun cocks]
- Shouldn't have done that.
[music continues]
[gun cocks]
[shots firing]
[dramatic music]
[horse whinnying]
- Hyah!
[water splashing]
[horse whinnying]
[music continues]
[water splashing]
[horse whinnying]
Hyah, hyah!
- Come on!
[music continues]
[horse snorts]
[wagon rattling]
[horse whinnying]
- Never gonna be ready for
winter.
- Oh, we'll be all right.
Come on, James.
- You have to visualize
it before you can
see it [chuckles].
- Hey, there's Bella.
[hooves clomping]
She's sure pushin' to get here.
- Thomas?
There's a woman in
town asking for you.
- You get a name?
- No, but she has a kid.
Blonde hair.
Pretty, a northern accent.
- Where is she now?
- My room.
She just paid me a lot.
- Let's go find out
who she is, huh?
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't.
Town rules.
You have to hide until
the threat is gone.
- Lin's right, Thomas.
I just spoke to Jericho and
he wants you to stay here.
Come on, Kid.
We'll be back when she's gone.
- Let's get some firewood.
[horse whinnying]
[soft music]
[music continues]
[upbeat saloon music]
[patrons chattering]
[poker chips clinking]
[music continues]
- Probably my favorite.
- [Hope] Mine too.
[Valerie gasping]
[gun cocks]
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Uh, I think I should go.
- This town is called
Redemption, right?
I'm looking for Thomas Keller.
Do you know him?
- No, Ma'am.
- I hear everyone in
this town is wanted.
Are you one of them?
- I'll be back in a little
bit to draw that bath.
[door opens]
[door closes]
- Hey.
- Oh, shit [laughs]!
How you doin', girl [laughs]?
- [Saloon Worker] What
have you been up to?
Come on, man. Lay off the damn
book
just for tonight,
just for once, Chief.
- Bella tell you
about our new guest?
- No, she did not.
[saloon worker laughs]
- Talk to me.
- Shot in the leg I think.
But Jericho, she
knows all about us.
Keeps asking for Thomas.
[music continues]
[hooves clomping]
[thunder rumbling]
[music continues]
[upbeat saloon music]
[Doc's throat clears]
- There's a posse
headin' into town.
Gonna be here real soon.
- How many men?
- 100 men.
Maybe more.
[music continues]
- What's wrong with you guys?
- Found Thalia and three
men diggin' up a grave.
- Who's grave?
- Thomas Keller.
- Why does Thalia care so
much about Thomas Keller?
- Thomas is the trouble.
Killed a Rockefeller, ain't
gonna just let that go.
[music continues]
[posse yelling faintly]
[wagon rattling]
[music continues]
- Hey, baby, you
stay here, okay?
I gotta go see.
- Hey!
Guys, you gotta come
take a look at this.
There's a posse outside,
and they're coming for me.
- They're not comin' for you.
Enough.
[music continues]
[chair thuds]
[alcohol splashes]
[bottle scrapes]
[alcohol sloshing]
[music continues]
[Robert's throat clears]
- So, where you keepin' my wife?
- Not sure who you mean.
[music continues]
- Well,
my horse is in your stable,
along with my saddle.
I want what's mine.
- You can go ahead
and take what's yours.
Then you can go,
'cause she ain't here.
- So you're gonna
protect a no good whore?
Hm.
[music intensifies]
[bottle scrapes]
[music continues]
[alcohol sloshing]
[throat clears] Well,
that's unfortunate.
[music continues]
[Robert's tongue clicks]
[Robert exhales]
Oh [throat clears],
I am lookin' for a man
named Thomas Keller.
Heard he took up
residence in your town.
- Oh, yeah.
You'll find him
just under his mark,
hung dead months ago [chuckles].
- Josh!
[pensive music]
[coyote head thuds]
[table rattles]
[music continues]
See, that ain't my brother.
So why don't y'all
tell me another story?
And this time make it real good.
[music continues]
Hm.
You must be Jericho.
- That I am.
- I've heard a lot about you.
Rumors of this town.
Well, I didn't think it
was possible [chuckles].
Buncha wanted criminals all
playin' possum [laughs].
My guess is arresting all y'all
would make me a very
rich man [chuckles].
Well, what with the
collectin' and the rewards,
ooh, it's all very tempting.
[music continues]
But I just came for one man.
Thomas Keller.
[knife thuds]
Wanted for the murder of Jess
Rockefeller in New York City.
Reward has been levied
at 100,000 U.S. dollars
and I want him alive.
[door creaking]
- God damn [chuckles], that's
the biggest reward ever.
- Oh, and I've been given orders
to kill any man who
stands in my way.
- Orders from whom?
- Charles
Hughes of New York City.
Governor Charles Hughes.
- Hm.
- This here's Kentucky.
My town, my rules.
- You know there's a wanted
man named Jeremiah McKenzie?
[Robert chuckles]
[music continues]
Yeah.
Yeah, that man fits
your description to a T.
What are the chances
I find a coyote
under his marker
in your graveyard?
Almost everyone in here
is wanted dead or alive,
and the law just
rolled into town.
So you either give me Thomas,
or I'll collect
on all your heads.
- Bitch!
- Fuck you!
[guns cocking]
- Stop!
[knife clinks]
[anticipatory music]
- I told ya,
the man you are looking
for is not here.
I'm gonna give you
one chance to leave
'cause there won't be another.
[music continues]
[Robert laughs]
[doors creaking]
- What are we gonna do now?
- We're gonna get outta here.
- Let's say we give
'em Thomas Keller.
- Yeah, I'll remember that
when they come lookin' for you.
- I don't have a
hundred men chasin' me.
- [chuckles] Only
a fool will believe
that he's only here for Thomas.
Oh, you don't believe me?
Why don't you ask her?
- You and I need to talk.
[pensive music]
- Clear these buildings,
gather up everyone inside.
Must sting to betray
your friends like that.
- Ain't nobody here my friend.
[horse whinnying]
- Hey, gather up some men and
let 'em know we mean business.
- [Posse Member]
You heard him, boys .
[horse whinnying]
- What'd she say?
- It's what she didn't
say that bothered me.
[horse whinnying]
[shots firing]
[objects clattering]
[dramatic music]
- [Grace] Mom, I'm scared .
- You're gonna
hide in here, okay?
- Okay
- Yeah.
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[townspeople groaning]
[firing continues]
[glass shatters]
[Bella gasps]
- Cover the doors
and the windows.
Make sure they do not get in!
[firing continues]
[bullets whizzing]
[pensive music]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[Robert yells]
- Stop!
Stop, hold your fire!
Have I made myself clear?
- I've got boxes of
ammo in the back.
- I'll get 'em.
[all yelling]
[fire crackling]
[somber music]
[yelling continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[Lin singing in
foreign language]
[Lin laughs]
- What is that song
you're singin'?
- My grandfather wrote
it and taught it to me.
He used to sing
it to many people.
- You talk a lot about him.
Sounds like a great man.
He scooped me up and brought
me to America when I was 12.
We worked on the rail.
We were part of these teams
that hung in baskets on the side
of the Sierra Nevada Granite
Mountains and set dynamite.
This taskmaster hated him
and cut his fuse short.
My grandfather didn't have a
Chinaman's chance to escape.
So, some years later I
found him playing poker
in the saloon.
11 dead, five wounded.
The sheriff was on
my tail for years.
Wanted dead or alive.
[Lin spits]
Hey,
and you?
Why are you here?
- Ah.
My life ain't worth spit, Lin.
I'm just buyin' time.
[Lin sighs]
[Thomas grunts]
Oh, where you goin'?
- I'm done. I'm done sittin'
here with my
head in the sand.
[Lin laughs]
- Wait for me.
[pensive music]
- I need to find Thomas.
- Lookin' to collect?
- No, please.
Where is he?
- Not here.
But once he hears
all this commotion,
what makes you think
he's gonna come to find?
- Because that man don't know
how to run from anything.
- Okay.
Six boxes of .357 and a
couple dozen shells of buckshot.
- It's not enough.
- Dad, we'll sneak under the
building and into the cave.
No one will see me.
- We go together.
Doc, I'll leave it with ya.
[pensive music]
[horse nickers]
[horse whinnying]
- Friends of yours?
- No.
- Come on.
[thunder rumbling]
- You first.
- Okay .
- I'll be right behind you.
- Okay.
- Go.
- I'm okay .
[hatch thuds]
[anticipatory music]
[horses whinnying]
- [Towns Person] Leave me alone!
Don't touch me!
- Get out from under there .
Come on!
- No, no[screams]!
[shot firing]
[knife whizzing]
[posse member groans]
[lantern shatters]
[pensive music]
[hooves clomping]
- Move it .
Come on.
[flames whooshing]
[woman groaning]
- They got Mary.
[Mary grunting]
[firing continues]
I'm gonna go and get Mary.
- Take it.
- No guns.
- Shit.
[dramatic music]
[shots firing]
[glass shattering]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
- Mary, get back inside!
- What the hell are you doing?
- You get back inside!
Mary!
Get down.
- Haven't you got a pistol?
- Nah!
- What are you gonna
do, throw rocks?
- I do not have any [indistinct]
- Use your God damn brains.
[bullets whizzing]
[music continues]
- [Jericho] Come on .
[energetic music]
[firing continues]
- I'm gonna go and get Grace.
- I'll go.
Stay here.
[anticipatory music]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[townspeople grunting]
- Mary, Ben!
[firing continues]
[music continues]
- Fuck it!
[Ben grunts]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
- Cease fire!
Hold your fire!
Stop, stop!
[firing continues]
[music continues]
Thomas!
[Thomas grunting]
- Thomas, what the hell
are you doin' here?
- Well, I wanted to find out
who's come pay me a visit.
- We're all here
for you, Thomas.
- Next time you try to
save me, grab a pistol.
- There's fire in hell, Mary.
Hot fire.
[wind whistling]
[pensive music]
- Thomas?
- Val?
[music continues]
- Mom.
[Val gasps]
[music continues]
- Thomas!
Thomas!
- Is that Robert?
[music continues]
- Thomas!
[door creaks]
[music continues]
[spurs clinking]
- Robert?
- Jesus.
Are ya surprised to see me?
- I thought you were dead.
- Yeah.
Well, you left me to die.
- No.
I tried to help you.
- Mm hm.
Yeah [smirks].
All my life my big brother
been lookin' out for me
when I did not need your help.
I'm tired of you
tryin' to save me.
[music continues]
Val in there with ya?
- I'm here!
- Oh, how nice!
Your daughter safe?
- You shot me!
- You deserved worse
runnin' off like that!
- That's enough, Robert.
What are you doin'?
- After what she done to you?
She's my wife, Thomas.
I do whatever I
want with my wife.
And don't you put her
in between us either.
We saw where that got us.
- Yeah.
- Probably best if you just
go with me and pay your dues.
'Cause if you don't,
they're gonna hang us all,
and I ain't dyin' for you.
- I ain't goin'
anywhere with you.
You go back to New York
and you tell 'em I'm dead.
- Mm hm.
- That's it .
[music continues]
[spurs clinking]
[doors creaking]
[Robert chuckles]
[Valerie gasps]
[pensive music]
- You all got 15
minutes to decide
where your loyalties lie!
Those who wish to
depart the saloon,
I'll grant ya safe passage.
Those who remain behind,
God help ya!
[music continues]
- Listen, I don't anticipate
any of you stayin'
on my account.
[thunder rumbling]
None of you owe me a damn thing.
There's no reason for
you to die here tonight.
- Oh, I got a reason.
I got one right here.
Couple more over there.
[thunder rumbling]
[gentle music]
And Ben's Jesus-y ass and
all three of his marbles.
Even you, Thomas.
Look, they know who we are
and they know what we've done,
so they're comin' for all of us.
The only way we get outta
here is if we do it together.
So, if I got me death tonight,
fuck it.
Long overdue.
[Lin speaking in
foreign language]
- Hell yeah.
[gentle music]
[Thomas exhales]
- All right, then.
[music continues]
[fire crackling]
[water dripping]
Hey.
What's your name?
- Gracie.
- Gracie Ann Keller.
- Yes, Sir, Gracie Ann Keller.
That's my name.
- My mother's name was Ann.
- I know, it was my idea.
- Well, it's nice
to meet you Gracie.
- Nice to meet you.
[Thomas chuckles]
[Valerie chuckles]
[gentle music]
- What happened to him?
- It took him a year to
recover from the burns,
and the Rockefellers are
hell bent on revenge.
They searched New York for you.
They spread west.
He got a deal that he'd find
you and bring you in alive.
He's obsessed with you.
He blames you for everything.
- And you rode all the way
from New York to warn me?
- Oh, I rode with
Robert most of the way,
but then I stole his
horse when we got closer.
- [Robert] Clock's tickin'!
Make the right decision.
And quick!
- I need a damn pistol.
- [Levi] That should
treat you right .
- Thomas, don't trust him.
[pensive music]
[fire crackling]
[water dripping]
- Let's load up.
[energetic music]
[singer vocalizing]
[vocalizing continues]
[music continues]
- Time's up!
If you don't leave now,
you ain't never leavin'!
- Those of you who are
patrons for the night,
gather your things and go.
[wind whistling]
[doors creaking]
- Hope, you take
good care of him.
- I will.
[floorboards creaking]
[wind whistling]
[pensive music]
[music continues]
[gun cocks]
[shots firing]
[townspeople groaning]
[music continues]
[firing continues]
[chamber spinning]
[townspeople grunting]
- Hope, let's go!
Follow me!
[firing continues]
[bullets whizzing]
[somber music]
[whizzing continues]
[music continues]
[sound muffles]
[indistinct]
[firing continues faintly]
[air whooshing]
[firing continues]
[anticipatory music]
[music continues]
[bullets whizzing]
[firing continues]
[townspeople groaning]
[gun clicking]
- I'm out!
Christ, if you ain't
gonna shoot, then reload.
[firing continues]
[music continues]
- What are you doin'?
- Let's go.
I need to get Grace outta here.
We can go out the back window.
It's dark.
They won't see us.
- Come on [groans]!
[firing continues]
[music continues]
- Thomas, please!
- I can't.
I'm sorry.
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[posse members groaning]
- Cover up!
[firing continues]
[glass shatters]
- Levi, back room!
[firing continues]
[pensive music]
[townspeople groaning]
[music continues]
[firing continues]
[townspeople groaning]
[music continues]
[firing continues]
[Hoodoo groans]
[music continues]
[both grunting]
[firing continues]
[towns person screaming]
[Mary screams]
[glass shatters]
[firing continues]
[bullets whizzing]
[rain pattering]
[music continues]
- Anyone left alive
in that saloon
better shove Thomas
out the front door!
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[Levi panting]
[Levi groans]
- You know, I could
live to be 100
and not understand your
loyalty to this God of yours.
Hell, got us all into this mess.
You know, you're
a good man, Ben,
and there ain't no shame
in keepin' your promise.
I can respect that,
but don't ask me
to understand it
'cause it don't make no
God damn sense to me.
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[Thomas gasps]
- Val [grunts].
You all right?
[hand slaps]
[groans] Hey!
- [Valerie] You should've
come back for me .
I was waiting for you .
- It was too dangerous, Val.
They would've killed you.
- Gracie, come on.
Come here.
I don't think so.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[pensive music]
- Come on, bastard.
Nice, come on.
- Doc?
I think I'm gonna
need your services.
- Help me!
[Hoodoo groans]
[glass shatters]
[music continues]
- Kid, in my room I
have a surgical kit.
[Hoodoo groaning]
- Oh, it hurts!
I apologize.
- Hey, shut up, Hoodoo.
Ya ain't dyin'.
[Hoodoo groaning]
[music continues]
[Hoodoo coughs]
- All right, Kid.
Give it here.
Give him some whiskey.
- Okay.
- [groans] It hurts!
It hurts.
- Okay, okay, hey, hey!
Not that one, that one's
gonna make him blind.
- Mary.
- Hey!
[Hoodoo groaning]
- Cool.
Here, come on.
Drink.
- All right, that's
enough, that's enough.
- Hand it.
- Bandage here.
[Hoodoo screams]
- It hurts!
- Don't mind if I do.
- Hey, hold him down.
- Hurts!
Okay, Doc, Doc, no, no, no.
Listen to me.
Please, listen to me.
I'll let you win
every time we play.
- You'd be dead before
I could collect.
- Please!
[Hoodoo screaming]
Listen to me, let go!
- [Doc] Wait, wait, wait!
- You ain't cuttin' me!
- Stop movin' around.
- Doc!
- You ain't cuttin' me.
- Okay.
- [Hoodoo] Doc, you
ain't cuttin' me!
- Stop movin' around.
- [Hoodoo] You have
your hands inside me!
- I feel it!
- [Levi] Come on, Doc.
- [Mary] Almost there.
[Hoodoo screams]
- I got it.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[Hoodoo gasping]
- It's shiny, it's shiny.
- Rest up, sunshine,
you're gonna be all right.
- You did good, you did good.
Good, good.
- Son of a bitch.
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
- Where's your big dad?
- Kid.
- Sorry, Sir.
- I'm fine.
- Everyone, get your weapons.
- Damn happy to see you.
- Feeling's mutual.
- About damn time you showed up.
- Mary, didn't expect
to see you here.
- Well, they broke in my
store and tried to kill me.
- You had some help.
- This is all the help I need.
Ben, put these on.
No time to fret over
some stupid promise.
[gentle music]
[thunder rumbling]
[belt clinking]
[music continues]
- I thought you threw
these away, Jericho.
- Would I do that to you?
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
- Hey, the ladies.
[energetic music]
[cork pops]
[music continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[belt clinking]
[music continues]
[singer vocalizing]
- Thomas!
Thomas!
I call a truce!
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
- I'm listenin'.
- Come to New York with me.
You'll have your day in court.
They'll condemn
you to the gallows.
Before you hang, I'll have
someone take
your place under the hood.
While they watch him
hang, you'll escape.
I'll make sure they never know.
You told them they all
could leave peacefully.
Why would I believe
anything you have to say?
[guns cocking]
Wait!
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
[music continues]
What, Robert?
- I won't let 'em kill ya.
You're my brother.
[thunder rumbling]
Hell, I can't kill ya.
We made a promise to
never hurt each other.
But I can't go back to
New York without ya.
[music continues]
I'm fightin' for
all of us, Thomas.
For you,
for our family,
for Val and Grace.
And when this is
all done, we can...
We can start again.
Very rich men far from New York.
[thunder rumbling]
[soft music]
[gun cocks]
- Thomas!
[shots firing]
[pensive music]
[thunder rumbling]
[Thomas grunts]
[music continues]
[Lin speaking in
foreign language]
[James chuckles]
- Hm?
- Hey, try this.
- Thank you.
- Good for the soul.
- Okay.
[rain pattering]
[thunder rumbling]
- You never told me
you're from New York.
- Yeah.
[thunder rumbling]
- What part?
- Five Points.
- What's the Five Points?
- [Valerie] This is
your bedtime, baby.
- Oh, it's in slums, James.
- I've never been to a big city.
Had a partner from
New York once.
He said it was a city of dreams,
opportunity on every corner.
Fortune's abound.
- I thought the same thing once.
I tried to make a difference,
but the rich kill
without regard.
No, Sir.
There ain't no dreams comin'
true for me in New York.
- "It's easier for a camel-"
- Camel!
- "To go through
a needle's eye-"
- Needle!
- "Than for a rich man
to enter into the
Kingdom of God."
- You got that right, Doc.
Sweet Jesus, mm hm.
Praise the Lord.
How!
[pensive music]
- That woman, she
risked her life
and her daughter's life
to come and see you.
[thunder rumbling]
She's got somethin' to say.
She ain't sayin' it.
Not in front of us.
[thunder rumbling]
[Lin vocalizing]
- I like it, I like it.
[Lin singing in
foreign language]
[anticipatory music]
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
- Surprised they let you out.
- There's a [chuckles]
trap door in the back room.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
- You're puttin' up
a hell of a fight.
Guess the rumor's
are true [chuckles].
Best of the best.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
Ain't that many
gunslingers left.
- They ain't givin' up neither.
[thunder rumbling]
- Yeah?
Mr. Brother's always
been hard-headed.
- Why don't you let me
bring him to ya alive?
[pensive music]
[Kelly chuckles]
[gun cocks]
- You're a roach
compared to him.
Bring him to me,
then we have a deal.
[thunder rumbling]
[music continues]
- "On the streets where the
blades of grass don't grow,
everything is like everything.
That's why children
who grow up in cities
are so incredibly naughty.
But love keeps up warm and safe,
even on the darkest of nights.
[gentle music]
[thunder rumbling]
And really good little
children get special treats."
[Valerie panting]
- You should let me
take a look at that.
[gentle music]
That book you were reading
of hers, it's good.
"Love makes you
feel warm and safe,
even on the darkest of nights."
- Shh, come here.
[door creaking]
What do you want?
- To talk.
- Hm.
What do you wanna talk about?
- I wanted to come back for you.
I thought about it every day.
[thunder rumbling]
But if I did, I knew
they would hurt you.
And I knew you'd find
a way to survive.
- It's not about that.
I don't care about the risk.
I need to be with you.
I've been waiting for
you all these years.
I love you.
[thunder rumbling]
[gentle music]
[pensive music]
[music fades]
[crows cawing]
[spurs clinking]
- Coffee?
- Great, thanks.
[objects clattering]
[pensive music]
- Wake up, baby.
We're leavin'.
Don't wake her up.
Here, your boots.
[wind whistling]
[anticipatory music]
[music continues]
- Hey, you.
- No one move!
- [Doc] Kelly,
what are you doin'?
- Surviving!
- He said he'd leave us alone
if I bring him Thomas.
I'm doin' what none of
y'all have the guts to do!
Outside, both of ya now.
- No one move!
- I'll kill him.
I'll do it, God damn it!
- Then you're all dead.
- Hold it!
Hold it.
I'll go out.
I'll go.
- We're goin' with you.
- Let's go.
Stay behind.
[wagon rattling]
[pensive music]
[music continues]
- Hey.
- Baptize me.
Matthew 3:14.
[music continues]
- Hello, brother.
- Let's go home, Robert.
- Yeah.
Let's.
[Thomas groans]
We ain't leavin' yet.
A lotta good men died here.
- It's me you want, not
these people damn it.
What are you doin'?
[gun cocks]
- Watch!
- Val, get back!
- Oh my God!
[pensive music]
[flame hissing]
- No!
[dramatic music]
[explosion booming]
[Ben groans]
[somber music]
[flames whooshing]
[glass shatters]
[music continues]
[Mary groaning]
[shot firing]
[music continues]
- [Robert] Put 'em in the wagon!
[Bella coughing]
[music continues]
- Give me your hands.
You got nine lives, kid.
Move.
- Hey!
You see anyone else lyin'
around here who's wanted,
point 'em out.
When she does, put 'em in a bag,
throw 'em on that wagon.
We're collectin' on all of 'em.
- [Valerie] Hey?
[handcuffs clinking]
[sullen music]
[music continues]
[gun clinking]
[pensive music]
- Get up.
[Levi panting]
[Levi coughs]
[music continues]
- Come on, get up.
- Where the hell do
you think you're goin'?
[horse whinnying]
[Robert grunts]
- You're hurting her!
- Robert!
Don't you touch them
again, you hear me?
[horse whinnying]
[pensive music]
- Gracie, come here.
That's a good girl, come here.
Come here.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
Hm, that's my girl.
[horse whinnying]
- I'm scared.
- Shh.
We are either gonna
raise Gracie together,
or not at all.
[music continues]
- Okay, fine.
- Hm.
[horse whinnying]
[door clangs]
[Thomas grunts]
[music continues]
- Could turn ya in alive,
but that would be more
trouble than it's worth.
- Eh, just as good to me dead.
- String 'em up!
- Robert!
Robert!
- Where's Jericho?
- Jericho's not in there.
- Well, find his body!
[music continues]
- You keep movin'.
Get outta town.
- What?
- You hear me?
I'm proud of you.
- No, no.
Dad!
No!
[fire crackling]
[door creaking]
[anticipatory music]
[music continues]
[rope creaking]
[cuff links clinking]
[horse whinnying]
[music continues]
[suspenseful music]
[horse whinnying]
[music continues]
- Sit right there.
[horse whinnying]
[key clinks]
[music continues]
[horse whinnying]
All right, Grace, let's go.
Let's get in the stage coach.
- Well, he's in there somewhere!
Get some men, and burn 'em out.
[Ben groaning]
[fire crackling]
- Jesus fuckin' Christ!
[Bella gasps]
[horse whinnying]
[ropes creaking]
- First time I've
seen you tight lipped.
- My, what a beautiful
morning it is.
[rope creaking]
- Yeah.
[pensive music]
Good a day as any I guess.
- Get in the wagon!
Hurry, now!
Josh, what are we waitin' for?
Hang 'em already!
- You heard 'em, hang 'em!
[music intensifies]
[music continues]
[panels thudding]
[ax whooshing]
[upbeat music]
[shot firing]
[hangman grunts]
- [Posse Member]
He's on the roof!
[shots firing]
[yelling]
- Thomas!
[firing continues]
[horse whinnying]
[wood creaking]
[Lin groans]
[James gasps]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[horse whinnying]
- Gather up the rest of the men
and make sure he's dead.
[firing continues]
[horse whinnying]
[bullets whizzing]
[music continues]
[Ben grunting]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[cartridges clattering]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[Jericho grunts]
- Dad!
- Doc?
Doc?
You okay, Doc?
- My leg's broke.
[head thuds]
[guns cock]
[all gasping]
[music continues]
- [Posse Member] Get up .
- Dad!
[gun cocks]
[music continues]
- [Thalia] Drop 'em!
Get up.
Move it.
[Doc groaning]
[all gasping]
[music continues]
[bullets clinking]
[gun cocking]
- How you's doin'?
[punch thuds]
Shit, son.
That all you got [spits]?
- When they done hangin', tie
him up next.
[music continues]
[wagon rattling]
[music fades]
[gun cocks]
[rope creaking]
[hooves clomping]
[wagon rattling]
[spurs clinking]
- Hey, gonna need some help
with this body up here.
[clinking continues]
[shot firing]
[dramatic music]
[firing continues]
[singer vocalizing]
[Thalia gasps]
[Levi gasps]
[music continues]
[vocalizing continues]
[Bella grunts]
[firing continues]
[music continues]
[vocalizing continues]
[punch thuds]
[Bella groaning]
[all groaning]
[rope creaking]
[Ben straining]
- Help me, Jesus!
Help me, help me!
Good God, y'all.
Help me!
Good God, y'all, help me!
- Come on, Ben!
- Help me, help me!
- Get your feet up!
- Ben, push!
- All right, all right!
- Come on!
- Help me, Jesus!
[all grunting]
Oh, good God!
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
Jesus, help him out!
- Good God, y'all!
Help me!
[dramatic music]
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- I'll be back.
Hang on.
[hooves clomping]
[music continues]
[Bella groaning]
[Thalia groaning]
- Help me!
[Bella groaning]
[shot firing]
[Ben groans]
[panel thuds]
[rope creaking]
[all gasping]
[pensive music]
[gun cocks]
[sullen music]
[music continues]
[Levi groans]
[gun cocks]
[music continues]
[shot firing]
[music intensifies]
[wagon creaks]
[horse whinnying]
[music continues]
[Thalia thuds]
- Bella!
Help 'em.
[Ben groaning]
[rope creaking]
[music continues]
[Levi groaning]
[Ben gasps]
[music continues]
[Levi gasping]
[Levi coughs]
[Lin gasps]
[Levi gasping]
[music continues]
- Come on, Kid.
Come on, Kid, wake up.
No.
Don't, don't, don't.
Kid, please.
[James coughs]
[Lin laughs]
[Bella laughs]
Oh my God!
[Levi laughs]
[gentle music]
[both grunting]
[pensive music]
- Enough!
- [Grace] You're hurting me!
- Shut up!
- Let her go, Robert!
- Move and I kill her!
- Robert!
- Shut up!
- You gonna kill
your own daughter?
Is that what you're gonna do?
[pensive music]
- She didn't...
She didn't tell you?
You didn't tell 'em?
Why?
Why not?
- Tell me what?
- You're afraid he'd leave ya.
Again!
Thomas, Gracie is your
daughter, not mine!
[pensive music]
- Mama!
[Robert laughs]
[music continues]
- This has to end.
I won't keep fightin' you.
So I'll make ya a deal.
Your life for hers.
Put your gun to your head
and save your daughter.
Do it and I swear,
the moment you're dead,
I let 'em go forever.
Do it, Thomas!
Do it!
Your daughter is gonna die!
Thomas, do it!
Do it, Thomas!
Do it!
Your daughter is
gonna die, Thomas!
- I'm sorry, Robert.
- Your daughter is gonna
die because of you!
[shot firing]
[Grace sobs]
- Come here, come here!
[Valerie gasping]
[singer vocalizing]
[horse whinnying]
[soft music]
[vocalizing continues]
[music continues]
[horse whinnying]
[vocalizing continues]
[music continues]
[music fades]
[hand thuds]
[light music]
- Where'd everybody go?
[Hoodoo groans]
[Doc groans]
- You all right?
- Yep.
We got one hell of
a mess to clean up.
- Yeah.
Been worse.
[all laughing]
- Course I shouldn't
drink too much
if I aim to get into heaven,
but it's goin' around
I'll take a sniff.
[Levi coughs]
- [groans] That's my
first time bein' hanged.
[Hoodoo groans]
- You save some of that for me.
- Hey, here.
- Hey, Ben, toss me that.
- Thank you.
Hey, pass it down.
[upbeat music]
- Oh, boy.
[rock song playing]
[rock song continues]
- All right, fellas, one
more hand, one more hand.
Anybody needs to borrow some
money, no problem [laughs].
And I got somethin' for
you like I promised.
- Mind if we join?
- The more the merrier.
I don't discriminate against
anybody [laughs].
Prepare to lose
your money [laughs].
I guess you all
wanna hear the story
how I collected the biggest
reward ever [laughs].
- You got your money.
- All right, good.
All right, then.
All right, sweetheart,
let's see what we got here.
[laughs] We still
gettin' married, right?
[laughs] Oh, look at that, dear!
Woo!
All right.
- Bring it here.
- Right there.
Here we are.
All right, fellas.
Fellas?
Kid?
Doc?
Whoa, no wait.
Now hold, hold on, fellas!
[gun cocking]
Where have you been?
Hey, look what I've got for ya.
Look what I got right here?
I got you some gold.
I saved this for ya.
I was waitin' for ya. This whole
time I was wondering'
where you were at, you two.
Fellas, so good to see ya.
Let's get these...
bring up your glasses.
Let's toast to Doc and Kid.
Woo!
[guns cocking]
[shots firing]
[blood splattering]
[upbeat music]
["The Gunslingers of
Redemption" playing]
[song continues]
[song fades]
["Oh Lord" playing]
[song continues]
[music fades]